Guide to the Richard White papers SC1323
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Teaching
  - Black Elk: 2 (Box 16, Folder 89)
  - Wovoka and the Ghost Dance, Wounded Knee Hist. 329 (Box 16, Folder 90)
  - Two Legging (Box 16, Folder 91)
  - "Traditional" Outlook (Box 16, Folder 92)
  - N.E. Courts - Patern. (Box 16, Folder 93)
  - Paternalism Missions (Box 16, Folder 94)
  - Dependency - Land Dawes / Burke (Box 16, Folder 95)
  - Dawes Act End of I.T. Hist. 465 (Box 16, Folder 96)
  - Work Dependency / Trade Dependency (Box 16, Folder 97)
  - Dependency + Education (Box 16, Folder 98)
  - Pick - Sloan (Box 16, Folder 99)
  - Hist. 465 Background Summary Conditions, 1900-1930 (Box 16, Folder 100)
  - Indian + Empire (2) (Box 16, Folder 101)
  - Intro (Box 16, Folder 102)
  - Collier: Cult. Econ 465 (Box 16, Folder 103)
  - B. Civic Ideal (Box 16, Folder 104)
  - Indian Rights Week 8 (Box 16, Folder 105)
  - Paternalism (Box 16, Folder 106)
  - Pasa. - Alaska Land Claims (Box 16, Folder 107)
  - Treaty Rights (Box 16, Folder 108)
  - Termination, Rights, etc. (Box 16, Folder 109)
  - Self-determination (Box 16, Folder 110)
  - H. Fowleer. Self Deter. (Box 16, Folder 111)
  - Political Change Hist. 465 (Box 16, Folder 112)
  - Ute Energy - Stephanie Romeo (Box 16, Folder 113)
  - Indian Ed. - Indian Experience (Box 16, Folder 114)
  - Indian Policy - 1980s (Box 16, Folder 115)
  - Econ. Develop. - Indian Experience, 0 (Box 16, Folder 116)
  - Hist. 465 Fed. Dev., 1960-1975 (Box 16, Folder 117)
  - Notes… Energy… (Box 16, Folder 118)
  - Sovereignity + Clippings tax (Box 16, Folder 119)
  - History of Wst. Hst. 329 Labor and Class Conflict on Frontier Lecture 18 (Box 16, Folder 120)
  - Hst. 329 Sources Second Half (Box 16, Folder 121)
  - BAE - Q+A BP (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Chippewa - Sioux St. Marie Expert witness correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - B. + Forest History Society book awards, 1980-1981 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - JAH, WHQ Pacific Historical Review Materials refereed, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - rough copies diss., 1982-1983 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Ecol. Article calls for use later (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - AHA, 1981 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Grand Traverse - Burt Lake Correspondence, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Sault St. Marie Sources, 1977-1978 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - PNW - Conference, 1981 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Book Corr - research, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - West + Folklore (cycle + paper etc.) (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Outside evaluations (reader), 1851 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Social bandits: corr/publishers, 1978-1981 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Franck Nursing, 1980-1981 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - El Paso Talk, copy, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Maps + pictures (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Sheep - hat, mose, 1937 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Interdepartmental correspondence, 1836 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Indian Commissioners, 1886 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - newspapers, 1863-1898 (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - Puyallap Land commission, 1906 (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - Original + revision sheets, 1898 (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - Wool, 1856 (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - Human Survey: Sociology surveys etc., 1939 (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - SCS. Administration + organization, 1939 (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - War - Military, 1855-1925 (Box 32, Folder 27)
  - War Related papers, 1856 (Box 32, Folder 28)
  - Wartime Res. Gen'l, 1855-1856 (Box 32, Folder 29)
  - Cons. Globe + record court cases, 1842 (Box 32, Folder 30)
  - Sec. sources res., 1925-1928 (Box 32, Folder 31)
  - Land Claims (Box 32, Folder 32)
  - Puyallup Land Commision Papers (Box 32, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence, 1880-1890 (Box 32, Folder 34)
  - Tacoma (Box 32, Folder 35)
  - Footnotes (Box 32, Folder 36)
  - Goodwin: American Experiments on Paid Motherhood, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 37)
  - Hamford Letter, 1905 (Box 32, Folder 38)
  - Higham History Culture Wars, 1997 (Box 32, Folder 39)
  - Hill Papers pamphlet (Box 32, Folder 40)
  - Carlos Gil notes, 1996 (Box 32, Folder 41)
  - Focal Diffuse (Box 32, Folder 42)
  - Village Locations (Box 32, Folder 43)
  - Terrance Martin Ft. Meigs, 1980 (Box 32, Folder 44)
  - Honors, 1988 (Box 32, Folder 45)
  - Env. History Syllabus Grades, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 46)
  - Early Exploration, 1973-1974 (Box 32, Folder 47)
  - Navajo Development Ruffis, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 48)
  - Papago Development (Box 32, Folder 49)
  - DeMallie - Pine Ridge Development (Box 32, Folder 50)
  - Peter Nabokov - Articles (Box 32, Folder 51)
  - Wishart: Cherokee Surplus (Box 32, Folder 52)
  - Etnohistory Seminar, 1988 (Box 32, Folder 53)
  - Grad Seminar - Islands of History Sahling (Box 32, Folder 54)
  - Grad Seminar - Wolf, Europe People Without History (Box 32, Folder 55)
  - Martin - Ethnohistory Seminar (Box 32, Folder 56)
  - Bill Cronon - Changes in hand - Ethnohistory (Box 32, Folder 57)
  - Axtell (Box 32, Folder 58)
  - Van Kirk - Many Tender Ties (Box 32, Folder 59)
  - History 786, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 60)
  - 822 Wallace, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 61)
  - Holder, Axtell (Box 32, Folder 62)
  - 20th Century Indians (Box 32, Folder 63)
  - Merrill Ferguson Zuni Repatriation, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 64)
  - Theda Perdue: Native American Women (Box 32, Folder 65)
  - Feminist Indians, 1989 (Box 32, Folder 66)
  - Natalie Davis: Iroquois Women, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 67)
  - Peterson: Women Dreaming (Box 32, Folder 68)
  - Nancy Shoemaker: Rise Fall of Iroq. Women, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 69)
  - John McManus An Economic Analysis of Indian Behavior in the North American Fur Trade, undated (Box 32, Folder 70)
  - Ray - History of Arch. Of Nc. Fur Trade (Box 32, Folder 71)
  - Early Trade (Arch A.), 1978 (Box 32, Folder 72)
  - Dean Anderson Paper, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 73)
  - Fur Trade S. (Box 32, Folder 74)
  - Rendezvous Fur Trade Articles (Box 32, Folder 75)
  - Ethnic Lit. / Indian Autobiography, 1987-2000 (Box 32, Folder 76)
  - Indian Lit., 1992 (Box 32, Folder 77)
  - Bay Area Partnership Read (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Hst. 239 Lecture 10 history of american west Sioux and Plains Resistance (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Background Hst. 465 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Learning through discussion handouts (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Hst. 329 History of American West consevation Lecture 22 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Hst. 329 Frontier Social History (sources, notes, etc), 1971 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - History of West Hst. 329 Corporations and West as Econ. Colony, 1890s (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Western Migration family, neighbors etc (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Little Big Man - Hst. 451 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Hst. Of West, 329 Indian Policy Indian Response (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Hst. 328 Order Settlement Lecture # 5 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Hist. 464 - Winter, 1985-1986 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - History of the West Lecture 7 18th Century and "new American" of Frontier (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - History of American West Lecture 11 American Col. Policy Land Govt., 1787 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Hst. 329 Lecture 3 Midwestern Frontier (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Western Economic Development Western History Lecture 16 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Myth and the West History of the West 328 Lecture 18 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Lecture 10 History of West Amer. Rev. in West (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - History 328 Red Shoes 6a Indian trade and politics, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - West History 120 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Hst. 329 Lecture 3 Western History Manifest Destiny-- Texas, Oregon, Mexican War (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Hst. 329 Questions the Searchers (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Hush Moon (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Hst. 329 Nevada Smith (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Hst. 329 Left Handed Gun, 1978 Winter (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Wild Bunch Comparison with Shane (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Notes on Shane Questions Lecture 16 (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Little Big Man (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - Hst 329 History of West Lecture 11 Technology and Ag. Frontier (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - History by- lausens, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - Hst. 122 Questions: Murrow Documentary on McCarthy (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - History 122 Lecture Post Modern World (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - Hst. 329 Western settlement environmental destruction, 1870 (Box 27, Folder 34)
  - History of West -- 328 American Western separatism lecture no. (Box 27, Folder 35)
  - The 18th Century: Frontier Society Hst. 328 lecture #6 (Box 27, Folder 36)
  - Lecture 10 Western History "Sectional Divisions" comm. Household conflict (Box 27, Folder 37)
  - History of the American West Hst. 329 Lecture 15 (Box 27, Folder 38)
  - History of the West Lecture 1 discarded entire, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 39)
  - Gold Rush (Box 27, Folder 40)
  - Hst. 329 History of West Lecture 12 Everyday life on the frontier (Box 27, Folder 41)
  - Lecture 6 Hst. 329 History of the West the Far Western Migrations: Oregon and California (Box 27, Folder 42)
  - Pop - econ cult, 1888-1892 (Box 27, Folder 43)
  - Settlement Process Cattle/farming (Box 27, Folder 44)
  - History of West Hst. 329 Lecture 18 Populism (Box 27, Folder 45)
  - Hst. 328 Questions -- Jeremiah Johnson, 1785 (Box 27, Folder 46)
  - Hst. 329 History of Aer. West Lecture 9 Legal Legacy of Civil War: Homestead and Morrill Acts, Railroad Grants (Box 27, Folder 47)
  - Hst. 329 Hst. Of Amer. West Competing Land Use lecture 13 (Box 27, Folder 48)
  - Hst. 329 Lecture 2 Land and Land Policy (Box 27, Folder 49)
  - Fur Trade + Indian Politics (Box 27, Folder 50)
  - Hst. 328 Lecture History of the American Frontier Economic Integration Nationalism (Box 27, Folder 51)
  - Hst. 328 West, Econ. Development 15a (Box 27, Folder 52)
  - History of the West Lecture 4: Comm. Govt. (Box 27, Folder 53)
  - Western History Lecture 14 Everyday Life on the Frontier (Box 27, Folder 54)
  - History 328 Lecture Social Order and fear of Social Breakdown (Box 27, Folder 55)
  - History of the American West Lecture 15 Mobility and Social Order on frontier of the Old Northwest (Box 27, Folder 56)
  - Group Projects Student Evaluations (Box 27, Folder 57)
  - History 329 Lecture 5 Plains Villagers: the Pawnees (Box 27, Folder 58)
  - 329 History of West Mountain Men (Box 27, Folder 59)
  - History 329 Lecture 4 New Mexico Mexican mericans Continuing non-Anglo cultures (Box 27, Folder 60)
  - Hst. 329 Lecture 8 American West Crisis of Settlement (Box 27, Folder 61)
  - Discussion group prep lecture (Box 27, Folder 62)
  - History of the American West Hst. 329 (Box 27, Folder 63)
  - History 329 Lecture 1 removal, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 64)
  - Hst. 329 Western Violence Lecture 14 (Box 27, Folder 65)
  - Hst. 329 West in 20th Century (Box 27, Folder 66)
  - Hst. 388 History of American Frontier Questions -- Big Sky (Box 27, Folder 67)
  - Hst. 328 Pattern of Settlement comm./household lecture, 1800-1830 (Box 27, Folder 68)
  - Fur Trade + interior Hst. 328 Lecture #7 (Box 27, Folder 69)
  - History of the American West Lecture 13 (Box 27, Folder 70)
  - Hst. 329 History of the American West Lecture 22 (Box 27, Folder 71)
  - Iroquoes - Huron Lecture #3 pt 1 (Box 27, Folder 72)
  - Hst. 328 Lecture 6a New Westerner: Jackson, Crockett (Box 27, Folder 73)
  - MA thesis, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 74)
- Books
  - Land Use, Environment, and Social Change: The Shaping of Island County, Washington
    - Indians - Secondary, 1824-1876 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Pre-war, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Resources, land use, govt studies - game, 1935 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Camana Is., 1884 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - N. W. History, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - N. W. History - Lecture Notes, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Little Legged Offlands magazine, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Indians Primary, 1861-1867 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Ebey Diary correspondence (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Annual Reports of Supts., Agents, etc, 1874 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence - Wash Suptcy, 1860-1869 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Stevens Many penny Correspondence, 1855-1857 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Logged off land surveys (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Lossed off hare, CUSDA materials (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Forest studies, 1900-1940 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Lumbering, 1890 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Settlement, 1850-1860 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Genl. Botanical Sc., 1861 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Whidby - unsent, 1989-1930 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Settlement, 1850s (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - The National Archives List of Documents Concerning the Negotiation of Ratified Indian Treaties, 1949 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Tax sales + abandoned lands, 1883 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - papers misc (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Flora + Fauna game - game comm. Fish (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Sales etc. Land, 1901 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - School + county lands (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - 1870's (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Boosterism - settlement early 20th Century, 1889-1905 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - I.C. Time, 1930s (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - 1860's (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Land Records I.C., 1903 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Probate, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Land Reports Comm. Of P.L., 1913-1932 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Newspaper in Island Co., 1891-1905 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Ebey's, 1881 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Darling Soer (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - I.C. Time, 1902-1932 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Tide Marshes + govt. reports, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Pop growth etc, 1860-1940 (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - Olympia - Unsorte, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - Census, 1910-1940 (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Census, 1880 (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - Diss. (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - Farming - Whidby, 1884--1895 (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - Stump land, 1910-1916 (Box 8, Folder 45)
    - Charts - Maps - tables (Box 8, Folder 46)
    - Mill Co. Land Holding Records Taxes (Box 8, Folder 47)
    - soil survey (Box 8, Folder 48)
    - Ebey, 1879 (Box 8, Folder 49)
    - Land Laws, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 50)
    - HSTAA (Box 8, Folder 51)
    - Notes to be - other, 1913-1922 (Box 8, Folder 52)
    - Newspapers, 1862-1890 (Box 8, Folder 53)
    - Copus, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 54)
    - Land Sales, 1869-1871 (Box 8, Folder 55)
    - Arsus, 1883-1885 (Box 8, Folder 56)
    - Chap. III (Box 8, Folder 57)
    - Townsites etc., 1848-1948 (Box 8, Folder 58)
    - Co. commissions Rodds. Lessons etc, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 59)
    - Cuteur - etc, 1924-1926 (Box 8, Folder 60)
    - Island County, Washington (Box 8, Folder 61)
    - Cruiser's Reports (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Reports - L.L.L etc. (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Archaelogy (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Geography (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - HSTAA 201, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Lumber Co. Correspondence - Policy (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Bio. On Speculators Mis. Lumber - Orders; Correspondence (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Whidbey Island - - Clippings (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Scale of hoss Cut, 1891-1899 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Student Letters of Recommendation, 1977-1978 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - PNU (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - 1890 - Land (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - First Contact Stories (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Treaty (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Personell W. Annuities (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Sawamish 1855-1857 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Fox Island 1856 -1857 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence 1870-1880 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Tolmie Letter/ Gates etc. (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Gates Meeker Gibbs Maynard Tolmie etc. (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Reports of U.S. Comm. Of I.A. (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - The Middle Ground: Indians, Empires, and Republics in the Great Lakes Region, 1650-1815
    - La Pot vols 3-4 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - To check against published Coucil (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Mid-term, 1855-1930 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Speech of Indian - S.S. (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - La Potherie - Savage Allies Genl. Notes (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Misc. unsorted Cambridge (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Check against test file (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Ordonnance (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - blue folder (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Unsorted Last Phase Research (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - OH- Huran + other intertribel (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Memoirs - trade - undated or misdated (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Penicault Man. (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Early memory (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - De Gannes Memoir, 1702 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - St. Cosmo (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - A Large Country in America (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Commerce Genl. Pre 1722 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - French, 1740-1746 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Wisconsin historical, 1744 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Canoe + tech (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - misc - fur trade (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Trade etc. stats, 1780s (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Kich Fur trade, 1763-1800 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Stevens: Fur trade, 1760-1816 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Stevens fur trade (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Captivity Broadside (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Thomas Urban Metro Studies, 1969-1981 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Suns (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Trade totals, 1780-1790s (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Conges (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Margry (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Slavic Journals (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Notes - Secondary for Nat (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Smuggling - trade etc - use later (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Deerskin (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Index to notes, 1941-1948 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Population village sizes, 1729 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Ottawa - Chefs Buos (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Delaware Prophet, et al (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Menominee Word List (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Note summaries (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Material Exchanges Perrot, 18th century (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Men/Women not used useful for notes (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Folklore (etc) (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Thett - undated msc (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Neal, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Pictures - projects Cambriose, 1770 (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - Pictures, 1720 (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - Prophets - Rel. (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Papoonhong (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - Reveryl (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - Social life - undated misc (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - Secondary - Western Indians (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - Town govt. (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - Govt. - undated misc (Box 4, Folder 56)
    - Indians - genl. (Box 4, Folder 57)
    - Chiefs G.T. (Box 4, Folder 58)
    - Maps, 1933-1934 (Box 4, Folder 59)
    - Census, 1780 (Box 4, Folder 60)
    - Misc. ethnography, 1792-1893 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - LeRoy + Leinuser Captivity (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Hetton - Wells (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Collections (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Amer., 1778-1779 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Americans, 1775 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Notes - sources, 1778 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Charlevoix, 1721 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Journals- guides + notes Bouguinville… Henry… Jones (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Published Journals, 1760-1770s (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Travels - JCB, 1941 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - French Journals etc. Genl. Comments, 1750s (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Ouiatanon Documents, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Civil Society (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Wars in West, 1680s (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Xerox (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - French pre 1670 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - French, 1683-1684 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - French, 1695-1697 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - French, 1670s (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Xerox, 1698-1699 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Xerox (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - White Report Chapter 1, Footnote 1 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Policy - English Parden host, 1947-1948 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Ill, 1947-1948 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Liquor - misc. (also see chrono. Files) (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Huron Manuscripts (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Presents (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Presents, 1753 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Medals, 1727 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Chick (2) (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Iroq, 1729 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Brandy, 1739 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Sioux (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - So wars, 1739 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - hunting game, 1729 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - French, 1680s (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Detroit journal, 1748 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Xerox, 1681-1682 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Xerox, 1682-1781 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Xerox, 1688 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - memoir, 1720s (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Docs., 1680-1682 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Gurds to mets (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Clifton correspondence (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Footnotes ch. 4 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Misc. trade stat notes (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Ch. 4: alliance (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Appendix A: fur trade (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Tenbrunsel Urban + Metro studies, 1750s (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Xerox, 1724 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - JR, 1630s (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - French, 1720 - 1724 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - French, 1730s (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - French, 1730s (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - English, 1784 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Vincent Vieth Humanities, 1775-1779 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - English, 1780s (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - English, 1780s (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Misc. - Cambridge Book (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - WHA, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - French Documents, 1725-1727 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - French Docs. by date, 1700-1704 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - French Documents, 1690-1694 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - French Documents, 1705-1709 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Myths - legends, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Secondary Anthro (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Gipsan (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Blasingham - Depopulation of Illinois Indians (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - La Population, 1944 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Misc. R., 1935 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Zoltuary Articles, 1701-1713 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Campaigne de la Colonie (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Zoltuany - Dev (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - PAC - R, 1756 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Carvers Goddard (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Notes onmemoirs etc. Raymond, 1928 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Tooker - Clans, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Anderson Proposal, 1987 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Hamell, 1984-1985 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Albers articles, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Lunn - Econ. Develop, N. F. - Fur Trade, 1942 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Wampam, 1782 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Michigan History, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Income tax returns, 1974-1978 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Wilderness Trail (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Woco etc current Reorg., 1747 (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Clifton (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - Charles Cleland - Fur Tradition, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - Meal Ferris, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - notes (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - Trigger: Amer. Arch as native history (Box 26, Folder 27)
    - Fur trade stats secondary, 1700-1775 (Box 26, Folder 28)
    - Wea Post (Box 26, Folder 29)
    - Trade secondary (Box 26, Folder 30)
    - Articles: liquor trade, 1960 (Box 26, Folder 31)
    - Rich-- trade habits and econ. Motivation among indians (Box 26, Folder 32)
    - University of Utah, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 33)
    - Secondary Anthro (Box 26, Folder 34)
    - Cadi Detroit, 1948 (Box 26, Folder 35)
    - C. Le Beau - Avantures (Box 26, Folder 36)
    - Jennings (Box 26, Folder 37)
    - Trigger - Children of Aataentsic (notes etc) (Box 26, Folder 38)
    - Delanger - Cadillac (Box 26, Folder 39)
    - Clifton - Leaders, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 40)
    - Tanner - Hidden Feast (Box 26, Folder 41)
    - French - biographical material, 1922-1923 (Box 26, Folder 42)
    - Settlement - reference, 1692-1693 (Box 26, Folder 43)
    - Acculturation (Box 26, Folder 44)
    - La Salle (Box 26, Folder 45)
    - Le Sueuer (Box 26, Folder 46)
    - Judith Brown - Division of Labor by Sex + Iroq. Women, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 47)
    - Ember - Women - As. (Box 26, Folder 48)
    - Missions articles, 1974-1977 (Box 26, Folder 49)
    - Black - Ojibwa Taxonomy, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 50)
    - World View secondary, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 51)
    - Tooker - Iroquian Culture Change, 1960 (Box 26, Folder 52)
    - Secondary Articles 6N (Box 26, Folder 53)
    - Climate, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 54)
    - Ramenofsky "European Disease and Aboriginal/Population Collapse", 1983 (Box 26, Folder 55)
    - Brown: Impact of European Presence (Box 26, Folder 56)